<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS Feed Reader</title>
    <updated>2025-04-10T20:18:07.900Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce ML training costs with Amazon SageMaker HyperPod]]></title>
        <id>81e630b8ad5f49e6704cd19294eef60b81c97bfb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/reduce-ml-training-costs-with-amazon-sagemaker-hyperpod/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T20:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore the challenges of large-scale frontier model training, focusing on hardware failures and the benefits of Amazon SageMaker HyperPod - a solution that minimizes disruptions, enhances efficiency, and reduces training costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anoop Saha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model customization, RAG, or both: A case study with Amazon Nova]]></title>
        <id>d27cd30df1af47607961e31e9dc4da441c9680a5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/model-customization-rag-or-both-a-case-study-with-amazon-nova/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T16:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The introduction of Amazon Nova models represent a significant advancement in the field of AI, offering new opportunities for large language model (LLM) optimization. In this post, we demonstrate how to effectively perform model customization and RAG with Amazon Nova models as a baseline. We conducted a comprehensive comparison study between model customization and RAG using the latest Amazon Nova models, and share these valuable insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flora Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate user-personalized communication with Amazon Personalize and Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>2a6669ddff2845bd386a4eeaee23e9b30e820f86</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/generate-user-personalized-communication-with-amazon-personalize-and-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T16:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we demonstrate how to use Amazon Personalize and Amazon Bedrock to generate personalized outreach emails for individual users using a video-on-demand use case. This concept can be applied to other domains, such as compelling customer experiences for ecommerce and digital marketing use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Grüebler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating regulatory compliance: A multi-agent solution using Amazon Bedrock and CrewAI]]></title>
        <id>2e45dd6fae9d8d4444a1b977cb69fcf32d7093c6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/automating-regulatory-compliance-a-multi-agent-solution-using-amazon-bedrock-and-crewai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T16:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how AI agents can streamline compliance and fulfill regulatory requirements for financial institutions using Amazon Bedrock and CrewAI. We demonstrate how to build a multi-agent system that can automatically summarize new regulations, assess their impact on operations, and provide prescriptive technical guidance. You'll learn how to use Amazon Bedrock Knowledge Bases and Amazon Bedrock Agents with CrewAI to create a comprehensive, automated compliance solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balu Mathew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixtral Large is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>22652c43a225c2a761388326148bfe423faac911</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/pixtral-large-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T15:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we demonstrate how to get started with the Pixtral Large model in Amazon Bedrock. The Pixtral Large multimodal model allows you to tackle a variety of use cases, such as document understanding, logical reasoning, handwriting recognition, image comparison, entity extraction, extracting structured data from scanned images, and caption generation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepesh Dhapola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement human-in-the-loop confirmation with Amazon Bedrock Agents]]></title>
        <id>ed096bef652f92e00fcc7760a2f1000a4f617964</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/implement-human-in-the-loop-confirmation-with-amazon-bedrock-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T19:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we focus specifically on enabling end-users to approve actions and provide feedback using built-in Amazon Bedrock Agents features, specifically HITL patterns for providing safe and effective agent operations. We explore the patterns available using a Human Resources (HR) agent example that helps employees requesting time off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clement Perrot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost team productivity with Amazon Q Business Insights]]></title>
        <id>a9d7b4d7c791e524858e019b1710caf02db66d2e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/boost-team-productivity-with-amazon-q-business-insights/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T16:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore Amazon Q Business Insights capabilities and its importance for organizations. We begin with an overview of the available metrics and how they can be used for measuring user engagement and system effectiveness. Then we provide instructions for accessing and navigating this dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillermo Mansilla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-LLM routing strategies for generative AI applications on AWS]]></title>
        <id>11cece0f5733d155762b5f0d6ea7db687d7d10c9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/multi-llm-routing-strategies-for-generative-ai-applications-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T16:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are increasingly using multiple large language models (LLMs) when building generative AI applications. Although an individual LLM can be highly capable, it might not optimally address a wide range of use cases or meet diverse performance requirements. The multi-LLM approach enables organizations to effectively choose the right model for each task, adapt to different […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nima Seifi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How iFood built a platform to run hundreds of machine learning models with Amazon SageMaker Inference]]></title>
        <id>7a4b58c9591b169928b1fa471d3979aa31b779df</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/how-ifood-built-a-platform-to-run-hundreds-of-machine-learning-models-with-amazon-sagemaker-inference/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T17:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we show how iFood uses SageMaker to revolutionize its ML operations. By harnessing the power of SageMaker, iFood streamlines the entire ML lifecycle, from model training to deployment. This integration not only simplifies complex processes but also automates critical tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an enterprise synthetic data strategy using Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>8f571a733f01cfd014785f1d93a457490a79be19</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-an-enterprise-synthetic-data-strategy-using-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T16:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how to use Amazon Bedrock for synthetic data generation, considering these challenges alongside the potential benefits to develop effective strategies for various applications across multiple industries, including AI and machine learning (ML).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devi Nair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Llama 4 family of models from Meta are now available in SageMaker JumpStart]]></title>
        <id>4eddc267f6794d17f803dc02f645ecc36d14fe75</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/llama-4-family-of-models-from-meta-are-now-available-in-sagemaker-jumpstart/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T22:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce the availability of Llama 4 Scout and Maverick models in Amazon SageMaker JumpStart. In this blog post, we walk you through how to deploy and prompt a Llama-4-Scout-17B-16E-Instruct model using SageMaker JumpStart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Punio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-tenancy in RAG applications in a single Amazon Bedrock knowledge base with metadata filtering]]></title>
        <id>01d6ecb090ec41e583a2f710c28a6dcffba0ea22</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/multi-tenancy-in-rag-applications-in-a-single-amazon-bedrock-knowledge-base-with-metadata-filtering/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T21:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how Amazon Bedrock Knowledge Bases can help you scale your data management effectively while maintaining proper access controls on different management levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Breanne Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively use prompt caching on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>6bb880c5ceadfbfb505422c571bca9606e3d7a68</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/effectively-use-prompt-caching-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T21:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt caching, now generally available on Amazon Bedrock with Anthropic’s Claude 3.5 Haiku and Claude 3.7 Sonnet, along with Nova Micro, Nova Lite, and Nova Pro models, lowers response latency by up to 85% and reduces costs up to 90% by caching frequently used prompts across multiple API calls. This post provides a detailed overview of the prompt caching feature on Amazon Bedrock and offers guidance on how to effectively use this feature to achieve improved latency and cost savings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharon Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced tracing and evaluation of generative AI agents using LangChain and Amazon SageMaker AI MLFlow]]></title>
        <id>4959a2b205b5a5decd8466087e09ec4d8b74954e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/advanced-tracing-and-evaluation-of-generative-ai-agents-using-langchain-and-amazon-sagemaker-ai-mlflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T17:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, I show you how to combine LangChain's LangGraph, Amazon SageMaker AI, and MLflow to demonstrate a powerful workflow for developing, evaluating, and deploying sophisticated generative AI agents. This integration provides the tools needed to gain deep insights into the generative AI agent's performance, iterate quickly, and maintain version control throughout the development process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandeep Raveesh-Babu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #471]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1626</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-471/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T01:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: We’re building an AI agent that investigates incidents with you—diagnosing the problem and even fixing it. Go behind the scenes with the incident.io engineers rethinking what’s possible with AI, one ambitious idea (and bug) at a time. https://go.incident.io/building-with-ai Models, models every where, so let’s have a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prompting for the best price-performance]]></title>
        <id>d94b0f4ec2954f3de2a4cfe7eaa5fa95b3fa942e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/prompting-for-the-best-price-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T20:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we discuss how to optimize prompting in Amazon Nova for the best price-performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claudio Mazzoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluate models or RAG systems using Amazon Bedrock Evaluations – Now generally available]]></title>
        <id>05b7b9ad4382e8322999e22c668f157a1e392d63</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/evaluate-models-or-rag-systems-using-amazon-bedrock-evaluations-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T15:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce the general availability of these evaluation features in Amazon Bedrock Evaluations, along with significant enhancements that make them fully environment-agnostic. In this post, we explore these new features in detail, showing you how to evaluate both RAG systems and models with practical examples. We demonstrate how to use the comparison capabilities to benchmark different implementations and make data-driven decisions about your AI deployments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adewale Akinfaderin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tune large language models with reinforcement learning from human or AI feedback]]></title>
        <id>48c3e3b3dc5efeb94262aea05e6654599ed278b9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/fine-tune-large-language-models-with-reinforcement-learning-from-human-or-ai-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T14:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we introduce a state-of-the-art method to fine-tune LLMs by reinforcement learning, reviewed the pros and cons of RLHF vs. RLAIF vs. DPO, and saw how to scale LLM fine-tuning efforts with RLAIF. We also see how to implement an end-to-end RLAIF pipeline on SageMaker using the Hugging Face Transformer and TRL libraries, and using either off-the-shelf toxicity reward models to align responses during PPO or by directly prompting an LLM to generate quantitative reward feedback during PPO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Curuksu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Lumi streamlines loan approvals with Amazon SageMaker AI]]></title>
        <id>102c2441982fdee3685ba828a9ca0b65479b5b7d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/how-lumi-streamlines-loan-approvals-with-amazon-sagemaker-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T14:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lumi is a leading Australian fintech lender empowering small businesses with fast, flexible, and transparent funding solutions. They use real-time data and machine learning (ML) to offer customized loans that fuel sustainable growth and solve the challenges of accessing capital. This post explores how Lumi uses Amazon SageMaker AI to meet this goal, enhance their transaction processing and classification capabilities, and ultimately grow their business by providing faster processing of loan applications, more accurate credit decisions, and improved customer experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Wirjo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AWS Sales uses generative AI to streamline account planning]]></title>
        <id>52e3e63ab2026ff681792d5981da33962b71d3c0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/how-aws-sales-uses-generative-ai-to-streamline-account-planning/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-03T15:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every year, AWS Sales personnel draft in-depth, forward looking strategy documents for established AWS customers. These documents help the AWS Sales team to align with our customer growth strategy and to collaborate with the entire sales team on long-term growth ideas for AWS customers. In this post, we showcase how the AWS Sales product team built the generative AI account plans draft assistant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saksham Kakar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaping the future: OMRON’s data-driven journey with AWS]]></title>
        <id>f16cf6c7a58d762f878d775f9dc43b35c783b167</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/shaping-the-future-omrons-data-driven-journey-with-aws/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-03T15:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OMRON Corporation is a leading technology provider in industrial automation, healthcare, and electronic components. In their Shaping the Future 2030 (SF2030) strategic plan, OMRON aims to address diverse social issues, drive sustainable business growth, transform business models and capabilities, and accelerate digital transformation. At the heart of this transformation is the OMRON Data & Analytics Platform (ODAP), an innovative initiative designed to revolutionize how the company harnesses its data assets. This post explores how OMRON Europe is using Amazon Web Services (AWS) to build its advanced ODAP and its progress toward harnessing the power of generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emrah Kaya, Xinyi Zhou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Workforce: using AI and Drones to simplify infrastructure inspections]]></title>
        <id>04b78f16db300204bffe27033678be60b2153340</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/ai-workforce-using-ai-and-drones-to-simplify-infrastructure-inspections/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-03T15:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspecting wind turbines, power lines, 5G towers, and pipelines is a tough job. It’s often dangerous, time-consuming, and prone to human error. This post is the first in a three-part series exploring AI Workforce, the AWS AI-powered drone inspection system. In this post, we introduce the concept and key benefits. The second post dives into the AWS architecture that powers AI Workforce, and the third focuses on the drone setup and integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Munoz de Rivera Gonzalez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ray jobs on Amazon SageMaker HyperPod: scalable and resilient distributed AI]]></title>
        <id>03ef5342d4fa59827d19a10b327008eefb8c1a85</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/ray-jobs-on-amazon-sagemaker-hyperpod-scalable-and-resilient-distributed-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T19:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ray is an open source framework that makes it straightforward to create, deploy, and optimize distributed Python jobs. In this post, we demonstrate the steps involved in running Ray jobs on SageMaker HyperPod.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Vinciguerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Large Language Models on Amazon Bedrock for multi-step task execution]]></title>
        <id>9c2192c48803ec4cc36965deeb8d9d69ac49481f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/using-large-language-models-on-amazon-bedrock-for-multi-step-task-execution/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T19:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores the application of LLMs in executing complex analytical queries through an API, with specific focus on Amazon Bedrock. To demonstrate this process, we present a use case where the system identifies the patient with the least number of vaccines by retrieving, grouping, and sorting data, and ultimately presenting the final result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruno Klein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AWS MCP Servers for code assistants (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>0f0758efc26b2b098306d2d40befc10e446f75fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/introducing-aws-mcp-servers-for-code-assistants-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-01T20:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce the open source release of AWS MCP Servers for code assistants — a suite of specialized Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers that bring Amazon Web Services (AWS) best practices directly to your development workflow. This post is the first in a series covering AWS MCP Servers. In this post, we walk through how these specialized MCP servers can dramatically reduce your development time while incorporating security controls, cost optimizations, and AWS Well-Architected best practices into your code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jimin Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harness the power of MCP servers with Amazon Bedrock Agents]]></title>
        <id>368e33e55b1864e4c9451eacd4e8a35bc846706a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/harness-the-power-of-mcp-servers-with-amazon-bedrock-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-01T19:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, MCP is providing agents standard access to an expanding list of accessible tools that you can use to accomplish a variety of tasks. In this post, we show you how to build an Amazon Bedrock agent that uses MCP to access data sources to quickly build generative AI applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate compliant content with Amazon Bedrock and ConstitutionalChain]]></title>
        <id>c89cfe8484e2a0dc07579752091c8f0a39823928</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/generate-compliant-content-with-amazon-bedrock-and-constitutionalchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-01T16:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore practical strategies for using Constitutional AI to produce compliant content efficiently and effectively using Amazon Bedrock and LangGraph to build ConstitutionalChain for rapid content creation in highly regulated industries like finance and healthcare]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sriharsh Adari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimize generative AI hallucinations with Amazon Bedrock Automated Reasoning checks]]></title>
        <id>ff4910af5afcdb549087c7560ecda6bc06aa7a81</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/minimize-generative-ai-hallucinations-with-amazon-bedrock-automated-reasoning-checks/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-01T15:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To improve factual accuracy of large language model (LLM) responses, AWS announced Amazon Bedrock Automated Reasoning checks (in gated preview) at AWS re:Invent 2024. In this post, we discuss how to help prevent generative AI hallucinations using Amazon Bedrock Automated Reasoning checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adewale Akinfaderin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS App Studio introduces a prebuilt solutions catalog and cross-instance Import and Export]]></title>
        <id>053eaa39a230cfa9c8dccb5e4e88f4bf6db25aed</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/aws-app-studio-introduces-a-prebuilt-solutions-catalog-and-cross-instance-import-and-export/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-01T14:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent AWS What’s New Post, App Studio announced two new features to accelerate application building: Prebuilt solutions catalog and cross-instance Import and Export. In this post, we walk through how to use the prebuilt solutions catalog to get started quickly and use the Import and Export feature]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Umesh Kalaspurkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6192</id>
        <link href="http://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/31/march-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T21:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pupdate March was reasonably dry (and even sunny sometimes), so the boys were able to get out for some nice long walks :) Milo also finished his third chemo protocol. I’m overdue a diary post about that, but the short version is that he’s doing well :) Skiing The month started with me skiing in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6192</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/31/march-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T21:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pupdate March was reasonably dry (and even sunny sometimes), so the boys were able to get out for some nice long walks :) Milo also finished his third chemo protocol. I’m overdue a diary post about that, but the short version is that he’s doing well :) Skiing The month started with me skiing in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build agentic systems with CrewAI and Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>68b5b6be421a9c45c1330006e55c94ba389f325f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-agentic-systems-with-crewai-and-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T15:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how CrewAI’s open source agentic framework, combined with Amazon Bedrock, enables the creation of sophisticated multi-agent systems that can transform how businesses operate. Through practical examples and implementation details, we demonstrate how to build, deploy, and orchestrate AI agents that can tackle complex tasks with minimal human oversight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Kipkemboi, João (Joe) Moura</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #470]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1624</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-470/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T01:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Intercom migrated hundreds of engineers from PagerDuty and Atlassian Status Page to incident.io in just weeks, improving resolution times, simplifying incident management, and delivering a better customer support experience. Watch the video case study. https://go.incident.io/customers/intercom The Sociotechnical Reality Engineer An SRE thinks about the meaning of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Guardrails image content filters provide industry-leading safeguards, helping customer block up to 88% of harmful multimodal content: Generally available today]]></title>
        <id>c0474d808f98914c3a2d5a9f9e67f6bbd8dc0ac2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/amazon-bedrock-guardrails-image-content-filters-provide-industry-leading-safeguards-helping-customer-block-up-to-88-of-harmful-multimodal-content-generally-available-today/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T20:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Guardrails announces the general availability of image content filters, enabling you to moderate both image and text content in your generative AI applications. In this post, we discuss how to get started with image content filters in Amazon Bedrock Guardrails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satveer Khurpa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating custom dependencies in Amazon SageMaker Canvas workflows]]></title>
        <id>3815925151d653d5902599a166eeda9cf55f641a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/integrating-custom-dependencies-in-amazon-sagemaker-canvas-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-27T19:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When implementing machine learning workflows in Amazon SageMaker Canvas, organizations might need to consider external dependencies required for their specific use cases. Although SageMaker Canvas provides powerful no-code and low-code capabilities for rapid experimentation, some projects might require specialized dependencies and libraries that aren’t included by default in SageMaker Canvas. This post provides an example of how to incorporate code that relies on external dependencies into your SageMaker Canvas workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nadhya Polanco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate training data and cost-effectively train categorical models with Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>9d1a09f0f854f508435803b3861bc3b81a65b83e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/generate-training-data-and-cost-effectively-train-categorical-models-with-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-27T18:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how you can use Amazon Bedrock to generate high-quality categorical ground truth data, which is crucial for training machine learning (ML) models in a cost-sensitive environment. Generative AI solutions can play an invaluable role during the model development phase by simplifying training and test data creation for multiclass classification supervised learning use cases. We dive deep into this process on how to use XML tags to structure the prompt and guide Amazon Bedrock in generating a balanced label dataset with high accuracy. We also showcase a real-world example for predicting the root cause category for support cases. This use case, solvable through ML, can enable support teams to better understand customer needs and optimize response strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumeet Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Amazon Bedrock cross-Region inference in multi-account environments]]></title>
        <id>f8f2c5545b48f7f16062818e5ef4bc5c200a9e0d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/enable-amazon-bedrock-cross-region-inference-in-multi-account-environments/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-27T15:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how to modify your Regional access controls to specifically allow Amazon Bedrock cross-Region inference while maintaining broader Regional restrictions for other AWS services. We provide practical examples for both SCP modifications and AWS Control Tower implementations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satveer Khurpa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker JumpStart adds fine-tuning support for models in a private model hub]]></title>
        <id>9857358e33e7d66c69b73702f0398485cfe6a07a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/amazon-sagemaker-jumpstart-adds-fine-tuning-support-for-models-in-a-private-model-hub/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-26T16:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are announcing an enhanced private hub feature with several new capabilities that give organizations greater control over their ML assets. These enhancements include the ability to fine-tune SageMaker JumpStart models directly within the private hub, support for adding and managing custom-trained models, deep linking capabilities for associated notebooks, and improved model version management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Karp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI-powered game design: Accelerating early development with Stability AI models on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>892451178febfe68679b4fcce9a5ca263df312fa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/generative-ai-powered-game-design-accelerating-early-development-with-stability-ai-models-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-26T14:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI has emerged as a game changer, offering unprecedented opportunities for game designers to push boundaries and create immersive virtual worlds. At the forefront of this revolution is Stability AI’s cutting-edge text-to-image AI model, Stable Diffusion 3.5 Large (SD3.5 Large), which is transforming the way we approach game environment creation. In this post, we explore how you can use SD3.5 Large to address practical gaming needs such as early concept art and character design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isha Dua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock launches Session Management APIs for generative AI applications (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>c24700deba0a4a7bc2ea0df992cd34791a0698fa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/amazon-bedrock-launches-session-management-apis-for-generative-ai-applications-preview/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T22:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock announces the preview launch of Session Management APIs, a new capability that enables developers to simplify state and context management for generative AI applications built with popular open source frameworks such as LangGraph and LlamaIndex. Session Management APIs provide an out-of-the-box solution that enables developers to securely manage state and conversation context across […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jagdeep Singh Soni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance deployment guardrails with inference component rolling updates for Amazon SageMaker AI inference]]></title>
        <id>c4e7759b3dce8220fd4479a352f73a5de0b278cc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/enhance-deployment-guardrails-with-inference-component-rolling-updates-for-amazon-sagemaker-ai-inference/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T21:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we discuss the challenges faced by organizations when updating models in production. Then we deep dive into the new rolling update feature for inference components and provide practical examples using DeepSeek distilled models to demonstrate this feature. Finally, we explore how to set up rolling updates in different scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melanie Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluate and improve performance of Amazon Bedrock Knowledge Bases]]></title>
        <id>743076ce678c9a68c93d522f5247b03207cc7b08</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/evaluate-and-improve-performance-of-amazon-bedrock-knowledge-bases/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T16:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we discuss how to evaluate the performance of your knowledge base, including the metrics and data to use for evaluation. We also address some of the tactics and configuration changes that can improve specific metrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clement Perrot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance enterprise productivity for your LLM solution by becoming an Amazon Q Business data accessor]]></title>
        <id>98018e526a37ea734fe87639bca1eb8958c074b9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/enhance-enterprise-productivity-for-your-llm-solution-by-becoming-an-amazon-q-business-data-accessor/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T16:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we demonstrate how to enhance enterprise productivity for your large language model (LLM) solution by using the Amazon Q index for ISVs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Takeshi Kobayashi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #469]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1622</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-469/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-24T01:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Speed isn’t everything. We studied 100K+ incidents to find out what actually makes for good incident management—from detection to follow-up. You can now view the recording of our latest live event to get even more info on the benchmarks, insights, and real-life examples from the report. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a generative AI enabled virtual IT troubleshooting assistant using Amazon Q Business]]></title>
        <id>79256449f8ddd8cdd46a760ca59140a15cbbcb3e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-a-generative-ai-enabled-virtual-it-troubleshooting-assistant-using-amazon-q-business/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T16:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how to build a GenAI powered virtual IT troubleshooting assistant using Amazon Q Business. This innovative solution integrates with popular ITSM tools like ServiceNow, Atlassian Jira, and Confluence to streamline information retrieval and enhance collaboration across your organization. By harnessing the power of generative AI, this assistant can significantly boost operational efficiency and provide 24/7 support tailored to individual needs. Learn how to set up, configure, and leverage this solution to transform your enterprise information management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasmine Rasheed Syed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Process formulas and charts with Anthropic’s Claude on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>ae9b55b2aa826df925218c47d3ae44aaaf467452</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/process-formulas-and-charts-with-anthropics-claude-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T16:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how you can use these multi-modal generative AI models to streamline the management of technical documents. By extracting and structuring the key information from the source materials, the models can create a searchable knowledge base that allows you to quickly locate the data, formulas, and visualizations you need to support your work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Cordsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate IT operations with Amazon Bedrock Agents]]></title>
        <id>6700ecfff1d189294e0988b7a82601914f0094ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/automate-it-operations-with-amazon-bedrock-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T16:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post presents a comprehensive AIOps solution that combines various AWS services such as Amazon Bedrock, AWS Lambda, and Amazon CloudWatch to create an AI assistant for effective incident management. This solution also uses Amazon Bedrock Knowledge Bases and Amazon Bedrock Agents. The solution uses the power of Amazon Bedrock to enable the deployment of intelligent agents capable of monitoring IT systems, analyzing logs and metrics, and invoking automated remediation processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Upendra V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline AWS resource troubleshooting with Amazon Bedrock Agents and AWS Support Automation Workflows]]></title>
        <id>2983c916fb110c5e83889c8bd47a5a8224976c6b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/streamline-aws-resource-troubleshooting-with-amazon-bedrock-agents-and-aws-support-automation-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T17:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS provides a powerful tool called AWS Support Automation Workflows, which is a collection of curated AWS Systems Manager self-service automation runbooks. These runbooks are created by AWS Support Engineering with best practices learned from solving customer issues. They enable AWS customers to troubleshoot, diagnose, and remediate common issues with their AWS resources. In this post, we explore how to use the power of Amazon Bedrock Agents and AWS Support Automation Workflows to create an intelligent agent capable of troubleshooting issues with AWS resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wael Dimassi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skiing in Austria (again)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6158</id>
        <link href="http://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/20/skiing-in-austria-again/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T15:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since returning to the slopes a decade ago I’ve been skiing with my daughter, but she couldn’t join me this year, as her industrial placement doesn’t offer enough leave. After various conversations with friends ran dry I eventually reconciled that if I was going to ski this season, it would be on my own. Inghams […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skiing in Austria (again)]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6158</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/20/skiing-in-austria-again/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T15:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since returning to the slopes a decade ago I’ve been skiing with my daughter, but she couldn’t join me this year, as her industrial placement doesn’t offer enough leave. After various conversations with friends ran dry I eventually reconciled that if I was going to ski this season, it would be on my own. Inghams […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silent PC upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6172</id>
        <link href="http://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/18/silent-pc-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T17:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR After 6.5y+ of service my PC needed a refresh – so it has a new motherboard, CPU, RAM and SSD, and I’ve taken the opportunity to switch to Linux. It’s still completely silent, but noticeably faster :) Background I built a Silent PC based on a Streacom DB4 case back in the summer of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silent PC upgrade]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6172</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/18/silent-pc-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T17:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR After 6.5y+ of service my PC needed a refresh – so it has a new motherboard, CPU, RAM and SSD, and I’ve taken the opportunity to switch to Linux. It’s still completely silent, but noticeably faster :) Background I built a Silent PC based on a Streacom DB4 case back in the summer of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #468]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1620</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-468/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T01:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: MTTx metrics fall short—learn the new industry benchmarks for measuring and improving incident management. Join us on Tuesday, March 18th to discover data-driven insights from 100K+ incidents and practical steps to enhance your response strategy. https://go.incident.io/registration.goldcast.io/webinar/going-beyond-mttx-measuring-what-good-incident-management-looks-like You Can’t Build More Nines No matter how bullet-proof you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>