<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS Feed Reader</title>
    <updated>2025-04-01T01:24:58.583Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6192</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/31/march-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T21:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pupdate March was reasonably dry (and even sunny sometimes), so the boys were able to get out for some nice long walks :) Milo also finished his third chemo protocol. I’m overdue a diary post about that, but the short version is that he’s doing well :) Skiing The month started with me skiing in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #470]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1624</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-470/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T01:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Intercom migrated hundreds of engineers from PagerDuty and Atlassian Status Page to incident.io in just weeks, improving resolution times, simplifying incident management, and delivering a better customer support experience. Watch the video case study. https://go.incident.io/customers/intercom The Sociotechnical Reality Engineer An SRE thinks about the meaning of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #469]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1622</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-469/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-24T01:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Speed isn’t everything. We studied 100K+ incidents to find out what actually makes for good incident management—from detection to follow-up. You can now view the recording of our latest live event to get even more info on the benchmarks, insights, and real-life examples from the report. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skiing in Austria (again)]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6158</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/20/skiing-in-austria-again/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T15:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since returning to the slopes a decade ago I’ve been skiing with my daughter, but she couldn’t join me this year, as her industrial placement doesn’t offer enough leave. After various conversations with friends ran dry I eventually reconciled that if I was going to ski this season, it would be on my own. Inghams […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silent PC upgrade]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6172</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/18/silent-pc-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T17:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR After 6.5y+ of service my PC needed a refresh – so it has a new motherboard, CPU, RAM and SSD, and I’ve taken the opportunity to switch to Linux. It’s still completely silent, but noticeably faster :) Background I built a Silent PC based on a Streacom DB4 case back in the summer of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #468]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1620</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-468/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T01:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: MTTx metrics fall short—learn the new industry benchmarks for measuring and improving incident management. Join us on Tuesday, March 18th to discover data-driven insights from 100K+ incidents and practical steps to enhance your response strategy. https://go.incident.io/registration.goldcast.io/webinar/going-beyond-mttx-measuring-what-good-incident-management-looks-like You Can’t Build More Nines No matter how bullet-proof you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #467]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1618</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-467/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T01:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: SEV0 is back. This fall, we’re bringing together the best minds in incident management for a day of learning, sharing, and networking in San Francisco and London. RSVP now—tickets are complimentary. https://go.incident.io/SEV0-2025 Introducing the Resilience in Software Foundation It’s been awhile since we’ve seen any updates […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using a Model to Model]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6134</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/03/05/using-a-model-to-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T15:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Once we get past ‘bullshit work‘, the primary enterprise use cases for Large Language Models (LLMs) appear to converge on various ways to make it easier to work with unstructured data. That’s because an LLM can generate an ‘understanding’ of the data, saving the painstaking process of getting humans to provide context. Of course […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3w]]></title>
        <id>https://liuning0820.github.io/2025/03/05/3W.html</id>
        <link href="https://liuning0820.github.io/2025/03/05/3W.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3W哪个更重要 人工智能时代，理解事物的 3W（What，How，Why）哪个更重要？最近我一直在思考这个问题。 最初触发我重新思考3W重要性以及在AI时代哪个因素更应该获取我们的关注，是前段时间看的一本书《理解和改变世界》里对3W 的描述。 该书表达在AI时代 What 不是最重要的，What 是对事物的定义和描述，但是这种定义和描述往往带有主观性，比如说情人眼里出西施。唐朝以体形丰腴为美，而现代以婀娜多姿者称为美人。再比如当西游记里的八戒被称为妖怪的时候，在而是观看的孩子眼里就是头可爱的猪而已。 如果说对How的上述表达我还能理解，该书对How 和 Why的重要性解读却让我陷入纠结。 首先他认为 Why 不重要，该书对Why的描述是Why 定义的是动机或者意义，而原因有时候会变。 比如为什么中国80年代要计划生育？为什么现在又放开计划生育？这些问题的答案会随着时代、政策和与当前的社会、人口老龄化的环境，经济背景相的变化而变化。 其次本书认为搞清楚How最重要，强调实践和掌握应用解决方案。 这本书让我深深地Lost了： 当我们人人对概念的本质进行深入思考时，我们的实践仅够学习应用解决方案（How），我们的时间仅够思考“如何”，而没有时间问及“为何”。 真的Why 不再重要了吗？ 当我重新梳理书中关于Why的示例展开来时，我发现有两种为什么(why): 当说为什么迟到，给出的答案是一种理由，这个理由也会变化;当问为什么中国80年代要计划生育时，为什么现在又放开计划生育，给出的答案也会随着时代不同而有所变化。 而当我们问为什么三角形2边之和大于第三边，为什么直角三角形两边平方等于斜边平方时，答案确是可证明。 这两种Why 有什么区别呢？ 当我带着这个问题问了LLM模型 Meta Llama 3.3 70B Instruct Turbo 后，给出的答案让我茅塞顿开。 我终于明白在AI时代，Why 还是最重要。不过这里的Why 指的是本质性为什么。新的时代浪潮下，我希望能够珍惜每一天，更加深入地探求和理解本质性为什么，寻找事物的真谛。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Toby Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #466]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1616</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-466/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T02:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A bit of a short issue this week, as I spent most of my weekend at my child’s first First Robotics Competition of the season. FRC truly is a microcosm of reliability engineering, balancing limited time and resources while trying to produce the most reliable bot possible. A message from our sponsor, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>