<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/index.html</id>
    <title>RSS Feed Reader</title>
    <updated>2025-05-10T14:13:54.544Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://liuning0820.github.io/rss-reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevate marketing intelligence with Amazon Bedrock and LLMs for content creation, sentiment analysis, and campaign performance evaluation]]></title>
        <id>0786623591ded64861ac461a9031cc138626a83f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/elevate-marketing-intelligence-with-amazon-bedrock-and-llms-for-content-creation-sentiment-analysis-and-campaign-performance-evaluation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T16:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the media and entertainment industry, understanding and predicting the effectiveness of marketing campaigns is crucial for success. Marketing campaigns are the driving force behind successful businesses, playing a pivotal role in attracting new customers, retaining existing ones, and ultimately boosting revenue. However, launching a campaign isn’t enough; to maximize their impact and help achieve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Namita Mathew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Deutsche Bahn redefines forecasting using Chronos models – Now available on Amazon Bedrock Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>d3ed23edd69b6b44950ec2b5fd67ca33b7652c7e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/how-deutsche-bahn-redefines-forecasting-using-chronos-models-now-available-on-amazon-bedrock-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whereas traditional forecasting methods typically rely on statistical modeling, Chronos treats time series data as a language to be modeled and uses a pre-trained FM to generate forecasts — similar to how large language models (LLMs) generate texts. Chronos helps you achieve accurate predictions faster, significantly reducing development time compared to traditional methods. In this post, we share how Deutsche Bahn is redefining forecasting using Chronos models, and provide an example use case to demonstrate how you can get started using Chronos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kilian Zimmerer, Daniel Ringler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use custom metrics to evaluate your generative AI application with Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>c51805fa560884cce1bbae1c377f2012aed6c1d4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/use-custom-metrics-to-evaluate-your-generative-ai-application-with-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T21:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now with Amazon Bedrock, you can develop custom evaluation metrics for both model and RAG evaluations. This capability extends the LLM-as-a-judge framework that drives Amazon Bedrock Evaluations. In this post, we demonstrate how to use custom metrics in Amazon Bedrock Evaluations to measure and improve the performance of your generative AI applications according to your specific business requirements and evaluation criteria.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shreyas Subramanian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #475]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1636</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-475/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T01:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com Anomaly Detection in Time Series Using Statistical Analysis I haven’t seen this level of detail in an article on anomaly detection in quite awhile. Still, the math is very approachable even if you slept through stats class.   Ivan Shubin — Booking.com A Key Incident Response Skill That Can Reduce Resolution Time TL;DR: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plex Media Server]]></title>
        <id>https://liuning0820.github.io/2025/05/05/plex-media-server.html</id>
        <link href="https://liuning0820.github.io/2025/05/05/plex-media-server.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[今天给大家推荐一款免费、开源的媒体播放器服务器，它允许您存储和流自己的媒体集合（如电影、电视剧、音乐、照片和家庭视频）到各种设备，例如智能手机、平板电脑、流媒体盒子和智能电视。 这款 Media Server 适用于各种操作系统，包括 Windows、macOS、Linux 和 freeBSD。它还可以安装在 NAS（网络附加存储）设备或 Raspberry Pi 上。 它是一款强大的流媒体播放器服务器，它允许您从本地存储添加媒体文件并进行流媒体化处理，使其能够在任何地方（本地局域网或者公网远程）的任何设备访问和播放。 下面就是我在家里局域网的搭建过程。 在一台 Windows 11 上安装 Media Server。下载地址是 Plex 官网。 注册一个 Plex 账号，登录后会提示你安装 Plex Media Server。安装完成后，打开 Plex Media Server。 添加媒体文件夹。点击左上角的“+”号，选择要添加的媒体文件夹。Plex 会自动扫描该文件夹中的媒体文件。 设置媒体库。选择媒体类型（电影、电视剧、音乐等），并为媒体库命名。 等待 Plex 扫描媒体文件。扫描完成后，您可以在 Plex Media Server 中查看和播放媒体文件。 在其他设备上安装 Plex 客户端应用程序。Plex 客户端应用程序可在 Android、iOS、Windows、macOS 和智能电视上使用。 家里没有智能电视也没有关系，我在家里15年前Sony 电视通过外接一个Raspberry 树莓派也能搞定。 7.1 在树莓派上安装Kodi 7.2 Kodi 里安装该媒体软件的插件 (PM4K for Plex)。 这样打开这台老旧的非智能电视机，也能享受智慧的媒体生活。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Toby Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a gen AI–powered financial assistant with Amazon Bedrock multi-agent collaboration]]></title>
        <id>57d2f86c6988c8d1677c4125febebcac23c21901</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-a-gen-ai-powered-financial-assistant-with-amazon-bedrock-multi-agent-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T17:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores a financial assistant system that specializes in three key tasks: portfolio creation, company research, and communication. This post aims to illustrate the use of multiple specialized agents within the Amazon Bedrock multi-agent collaboration capability, with particular emphasis on their application in financial analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suheel Farooq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordFinder app: Harnessing generative AI on AWS for aphasia communication]]></title>
        <id>5f4d2fb57148ca4849a3f3cf7f00211c894e199f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/wordfinder-app-harnessing-generative-ai-on-aws-for-aphasia-communication/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we showcase how Dr. Kori Ramajoo, Dr. Sonia Brownsett, Prof. David Copland, from QARC, and Scott Harding, a person living with aphasia, used AWS services to develop WordFinder, a mobile, cloud-based solution that helps individuals with aphasia increase their independence through the use of AWS generative AI technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kori Ramijoo, Scott Harding, Sonia Brownsett, David Copland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get faster and actionable AWS Trusted Advisor insights to make data-driven decisions using Amazon Q Business]]></title>
        <id>542285c21d3edb8e59de58195262f4dba32ed628</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/get-faster-and-actionable-aws-trusted-advisor-insights-to-make-data-driven-decisions-using-amazon-q-business/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we show how to create an application using Amazon Q Business with Jira integration that used a dataset containing a Trusted Advisor detailed report. This solution demonstrates how to use new generative AI services like Amazon Q Business to get data insights faster and make them actionable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satish Bhonsle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices for Meta Llama 3.2 multimodal fine-tuning on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>d7d5eaef99dba985314485739c892bebdc7ee128</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/best-practices-for-meta-llama-3-2-multimodal-fine-tuning-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T21:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we share comprehensive best practices and scientific insights for fine-tuning Meta Llama 3.2 multimodal models on Amazon Bedrock. By following these guidelines, you can fine-tune smaller, more cost-effective models to achieve performance that rivals or even surpasses much larger models—potentially reducing both inference costs and latency, while maintaining high accuracy for your specific use case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yanyan Zhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extend large language models powered by Amazon SageMaker AI using Model Context Protocol]]></title>
        <id>bcc75f5647ad075626836f246151b92ad7c3f89e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/extend-large-language-models-powered-by-amazon-sagemaker-ai-using-model-context-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T17:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MCP proposed by Anthropic offers a standardized way of connecting FMs to data sources, and now you can use this capability with SageMaker AI. In this post, we presented an example of combining the power of SageMaker AI and MCP to build an application that offers a new perspective on loan underwriting through specialized roles and automated workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mona Mona</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate document translation and standardization with Amazon Bedrock and Amazon Translate]]></title>
        <id>0bba01f82b9dde8048d99ffbaf537a0130290f65</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/automate-document-translation-and-standardization-with-amazon-bedrock-and-amazon-translate/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we show how you can automate language localization through translating documents using Amazon Web Services (AWS). The solution combines Amazon Bedrock and AWS Serverless technologies, a suite of fully managed event-driven services for running code, managing data, and integrating applications—all without managing servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nadhya Polanco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous mortgage processing using Amazon Bedrock Data Automation and Amazon Bedrock Agents]]></title>
        <id>4632f90cc355bfca6fd537469befe1ce556558a1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/autonomous-mortgage-processing-using-amazon-bedrock-data-automation-and-amazon-bedrock-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T16:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we introduce agentic automatic mortgage approval, a next-generation sample solution that uses autonomous AI agents powered by Amazon Bedrock Agents and Amazon Bedrock Data Automation. These agents orchestrate the entire mortgage approval process—intelligently verifying documents, assessing risk, and making data-driven decisions with minimal human intervention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wrick Talukdar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6250</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/05/01/april-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T09:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pupdate April has been rather nice, which has given the opportunity for plenty of long walks :) Florida We started the month in Florida, more on that in its own post – Florida 2025. Bike bother Vespa I mentioned my broken Vespa last month, and returned from Florida to a diagnosis of low compression, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Model Distillation: Boost function calling accuracy while reducing cost and latency]]></title>
        <id>218ca171ee4d12bdd12a91241b0ac16e3df57b57</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/amazon-bedrock-model-distillation-boost-function-calling-accuracy-while-reducing-cost-and-latency/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T01:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we highlight the advanced data augmentation techniques and performance improvements in Amazon Bedrock Model Distillation with Meta's Llama model family. This technique transfers knowledge from larger, more capable foundation models (FMs) that act as teachers to smaller, more efficient models (students), creating specialized models that excel at specific tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yanyan Zhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build public-facing generative AI applications using Amazon Q Business for anonymous users]]></title>
        <id>7e0fb8f751ee74945810096690182ca7b6ea69d0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-public-facing-generative-ai-applications-using-amazon-q-business-for-anonymous-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce that Amazon Q Business now supports anonymous user access. With this new feature, you can now create Amazon Q Business applications with anonymous user mode, where user authentication is not required and content is publicly accessible. In this post, we demonstrate how to build a public-facing generative AI application using Amazon Q Business for anonymous users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vishnu Elangovan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FloQast builds an AI-powered accounting transformation solution with Anthropic’s Claude 3 on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>e4bec8c22944b630a47d0ef10237bf71553bb9d7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/floqast-builds-an-ai-powered-accounting-transformation-solution-with-anthropics-claude-3-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T18:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we share how FloQast built an AI-powered accounting transaction solution using Anthropic’s Claude 3 on Amazon Bedrock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kartik Bhatnagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insights in implementing production-ready solutions with generative AI]]></title>
        <id>e442204e2212b3e0f2a265e22354796fe882cb45</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/insights-in-implementing-production-ready-solutions-with-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T18:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As generative AI revolutionizes industries, organizations are eager to harness its potential. However, the journey from production-ready solutions to full-scale implementation can present distinct operational and technical considerations. This post explores key insights and lessons learned from AWS customers in Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) who have successfully navigated this transition, providing a roadmap for others looking to follow suit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giorgio Pessot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible AI in action: How Data Reply red teaming supports generative AI safety on AWS]]></title>
        <id>0461f1e9e2ede75141c4b21edb2e51224ab8b422</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/responsible-ai-in-action-how-data-reply-red-teaming-supports-generative-ai-safety-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how AWS services can be seamlessly integrated with open source tools to help establish a robust red teaming mechanism within your organization. Specifically, we discuss Data Reply’s red teaming solution, a comprehensive blueprint to enhance AI safety and responsible AI practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassandre Vandeputte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InterVision accelerates AI development using AWS LLM League and Amazon SageMaker AI]]></title>
        <id>45ccc28d0b7f4cbdb32d71e45329d168b9ea8260</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/intervision-accelerates-ai-development-using-aws-llm-league-and-amazon-sagemaker-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how AWS LLM League’s gamified enablement accelerates partners’ practical AI development capabilities, while showcasing how fine-tuning smaller language models can deliver cost-effective, specialized solutions for specific industry needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vu Le</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Amazon Nova migration performance with data-aware prompt optimization]]></title>
        <id>09adbaa09f66d966d0056383025cb1cf99245bf6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/improve-amazon-nova-migration-performance-with-data-aware-prompt-optimization/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T16:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we present an LLM migration paradigm and architecture, including a continuous process of model evaluation, prompt generation using Amazon Bedrock, and data-aware optimization. The solution evaluates the model performance before migration and iteratively optimizes the Amazon Nova model prompts using user-provided dataset and objective metrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yunfei Bai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize Amazon Nova models to improve tool usage]]></title>
        <id>8665f6092a91a35da1d3f6ba2973900cc4bcb4d7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/customize-amazon-nova-models-to-improve-tool-usage/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T17:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we demonstrate model customization (fine-tuning) for tool use with Amazon Nova. We first introduce a tool usage use case, and gave details about the dataset. We walk through the details of Amazon Nova specific data formatting and showed how to do tool calling through the Converse and Invoke APIs in Amazon Bedrock. After getting the baseline results from Amazon Nova models, we explain in detail the fine-tuning process, hosting fine-tuned models with provisioned throughput, and using the fine-tuned Amazon Nova models for inference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baishali Chaudhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluate Amazon Bedrock Agents with Ragas and LLM-as-a-judge]]></title>
        <id>2881e224e92fe270c8629a96ed58405bdd40ef66</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/evaluate-amazon-bedrock-agents-with-ragas-and-llm-as-a-judge/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T15:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we introduced the Open Source Bedrock Agent Evaluation framework, a Langfuse-integrated solution that streamlines the agent development process. We demonstrated how this evaluation framework can be integrated with pharmaceutical research agents. We used it to evaluate agent performance against biomarker questions and sent traces to Langfuse to view evaluation metrics across question types.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishiraj Chandra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #474]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1632</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-474/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T01:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: We’ve just raised $62M at incident.io to build AI agents that resolve incidents with you. See how we’re pioneering a new era of incident management. https://go.incident.io/blog/incident.io-raises-62m Why do we do blameless incident reviews? This is a truly outstanding article about blameless incident analysis! Beyond just “why”, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise-grade natural language to SQL generation using LLMs: Balancing accuracy, latency, and scale]]></title>
        <id>c51652081e86ead377a26a3a9bd261c58ad9b6d7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/enterprise-grade-natural-language-to-sql-generation-using-llms-balancing-accuracy-latency-and-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T16:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, the AWS and Cisco teams unveil a new methodical approach that addresses the challenges of enterprise-grade SQL generation. The teams were able to reduce the complexity of the NL2SQL process while delivering higher accuracy and better overall performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Renuka Kumar, Toby Fotherby, Shweta Keshavanarayana, Thomas Matthew, Daniel Vaquero, Atul Varshneya, and Jessica Wu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Field Experience reduced cost and delivered low latency and high performance with Amazon Nova Lite foundation model]]></title>
        <id>b61aa066650e752aa18cf2f35ea64f43fc6494dd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/aws-field-experience-reduced-cost-and-delivered-low-latency-and-high-performance-with-amazon-nova-lite-foundation-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T16:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AFX team’s product migration to the Nova Lite model has delivered tangible enterprise value by enhancing sales workflows. By migrating to the Amazon Nova Lite model, the team has not only achieved significant cost savings and reduced latency, but has also empowered sellers with a leading intelligent and reliable solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anuj Jauhari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combine keyword and semantic search for text and images using Amazon Bedrock and Amazon OpenSearch Service]]></title>
        <id>076f38fa1e653e66b4ee7a2c015362cd4def8cab</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/combine-keyword-and-semantic-search-for-text-and-images-using-amazon-bedrock-and-amazon-opensearch-service/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T16:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we walk you through how to build a hybrid search solution using OpenSearch Service powered by multimodal embeddings from the Amazon Titan Multimodal Embeddings G1 model through Amazon Bedrock. This solution demonstrates how you can enable users to submit both text and images as queries to retrieve relevant results from a sample retail image dataset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Renan Bertolazzi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an AI-powered document processing platform with open source NER model and LLM on Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>9e72b003073ae43dbaa395716df908ed35ef1126</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-an-ai-powered-document-processing-platform-with-open-source-ner-model-and-llm-on-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T16:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we discuss how you can build an AI-powered document processing platform with open source NER and LLMs on SageMaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Biso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect sensitive data in RAG applications with Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>bba533050dafb54c11c12b0d447bb00cfbe78138</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/protect-sensitive-data-in-rag-applications-with-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T16:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore two approaches for securing sensitive data in RAG applications using Amazon Bedrock. The first approach focused on identifying and redacting sensitive data before ingestion into an Amazon Bedrock knowledge base, and the second demonstrated a fine-grained RBAC pattern for managing access to sensitive information during retrieval. These solutions represent just two possible approaches among many for securing sensitive data in generative AI applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Praveen Chamarthi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharge your LLM performance with Amazon SageMaker Large Model Inference container v15]]></title>
        <id>6ef052f783f7dd9cf7b2d547d981fbeead415403</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/supercharge-your-llm-performance-with-amazon-sagemaker-large-model-inference-container-v15/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T17:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce the launch of Amazon SageMaker Large Model Inference (LMI) container v15, powered by vLLM 0.8.4 with support for the vLLM V1 engine. This release introduces significant performance improvements, expanded model compatibility with multimodality (that is, the ability to understand and analyze text-to-text, images-to-text, and text-to-images data), and provides built-in integration with vLLM to help you seamlessly deploy and serve large language models (LLMs) with the highest performance at scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Gangasani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accuracy evaluation framework for Amazon Q Business – Part 2]]></title>
        <id>0200f5b5a84c5cfe58ad7559beb8783a7534b5c3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/accuracy-evaluation-framework-for-amazon-q-business-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T17:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first post of this series, we introduced a comprehensive evaluation framework for Amazon Q Business, a fully managed Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) solution that uses your company’s proprietary data without the complexity of managing large language models (LLMs). The first post focused on selecting appropriate use cases, preparing data, and implementing metrics to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rui Cardoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Amazon Bedrock Intelligent Prompt Routing for cost and latency benefits]]></title>
        <id>b8b4483af4f40eec3e0f5250ff4f69f83df4665b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/use-amazon-bedrock-intelligent-prompt-routing-for-cost-and-latency-benefits/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T17:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re happy to announce the general availability of Amazon Bedrock Intelligent Prompt Routing. In this blog post, we detail various highlights from our internal testing, how you can get started, and point out some caveats and best practices. We encourage you to incorporate Amazon Bedrock Intelligent Prompt Routing into your new and existing generative AI applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shreyas Subramanian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Infosys improved accessibility for Event Knowledge using Amazon Nova Pro, Amazon Bedrock and Amazon Elemental Media Services]]></title>
        <id>3f1d20932667f2fb527e7125ed86380d4509e167</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/how-infosys-improved-accessibility-for-event-knowledge-using-amazon-nova-pro-amazon-bedrock-and-amazon-elemental-media-services/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T17:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how Infosys developed Infosys Event AI to unlock the insights generated from events and conferences. Through its suite of features—including real-time transcription, intelligent summaries, and an interactive chat assistant—Infosys Event AI makes event knowledge accessible and provides an immersive engagement solution for the attendees, during and after the event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aparajithan Vaidyanathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Prompt Optimization Drives LLM Applications Innovation for Yuewen Group]]></title>
        <id>b08d7e14274d10a8f864b2e11e6ff5c6db9c8d05</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/amazon-bedrock-prompt-optimization-drives-llm-applications-innovation-for-yuewen-group/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T22:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are excited to announce the availability of Prompt Optimization on Amazon Bedrock. With this capability, you can now optimize your prompts for several use cases with a single API call or a click of a button on the Amazon Bedrock console. In this blog post, we discuss how Prompt Optimization improves the performance of large language models (LLMs) for intelligent text processing task in Yuewen Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wang Rui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a location-aware agent using Amazon Bedrock Agents and Foursquare APIs]]></title>
        <id>662f5bb7bcd5c548f57a81fa71398f9a2314ae3a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-a-location-aware-agent-using-amazon-bedrock-agents-and-foursquare-apis/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we combine Amazon Bedrock Agents and Foursquare APIs to demonstrate how you can use a location-aware agent to bring personalized responses to your users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an automated generative AI solution evaluation pipeline with Amazon Nova]]></title>
        <id>555bf4bfc1b42438c8e3d7a033099ecab9eceb70</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-an-automated-generative-ai-solution-evaluation-pipeline-with-amazon-nova/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T17:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore the importance of evaluating LLMs in the context of generative AI applications, highlighting the challenges posed by issues like hallucinations and biases. We introduced a comprehensive solution using AWS services to automate the evaluation process, allowing for continuous monitoring and assessment of LLM performance. By using tools like the FMeval Library, Ragas, LLMeter, and Step Functions, the solution provides flexibility and scalability, meeting the evolving needs of LLM consumers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepak Dalakoti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #473]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1630</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-473/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T03:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: We’ve just raised $62M at incident.io to build AI agents that resolve incidents with you. See how we’re pioneering a new era of incident management. https://go.incident.io/blog/incident.io-raises-62m Scaling Nextdoor’s Datastores: Part 5 In this final installment of the Scaling Nextdoor’s Datastores blog series, we detail how the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a FinOps agent using Amazon Bedrock with multi-agent capability and Amazon Nova as the foundation model]]></title>
        <id>34ecb60fc8973268c2a75ff1f7cfb3040379d77e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-a-finops-agent-using-amazon-bedrock-with-multi-agent-capability-and-amazon-nova-as-the-foundation-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T17:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we use the multi-agent feature of Amazon Bedrock to demonstrate a powerful and innovative approach to AWS cost management. By using the advanced capabilities of Amazon Nova FMs, we’ve developed a solution that showcases how AI-driven agents can revolutionize the way organizations analyze, optimize, and manage their AWS costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salman Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stream ingest data from Kafka to Amazon Bedrock Knowledge Bases using custom connectors]]></title>
        <id>2e23ddc4379ed193ac091573464b7d61c6456830</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/stream-ingest-data-from-kafka-to-amazon-bedrock-knowledge-bases-using-custom-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T17:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this post, we implement a RAG architecture with Amazon Bedrock Knowledge Bases using a custom connector and topics built with Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka (Amazon MSK) for a user who may be interested to understand stock price trends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prabhakar Chandrasekaran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add Zoom as a data accessor to your Amazon Q index]]></title>
        <id>d40b6daa165240c8a62c0769ee68d0017aed4e71</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/add-zoom-as-a-data-accessor-to-your-amazon-q-index/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T18:19:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how Zoom users can access their Amazon Q Business enterprise data directly within their Zoom interface, alleviating the need to switch between applications while maintaining enterprise security boundaries. Organizations can now configure Zoom as a data accessor in Amazon Q Business, enabling seamless integration between their Amazon Q index and Zoom AI Companion. This integration allows users to access their enterprise knowledge in a controlled manner directly within the Zoom platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Girling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of quality assurance: Shift-left testing with QyrusAI and Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>74bede199a93faffc812ff4903823b984742f4ce</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/the-future-of-quality-assurance-shift-left-testing-with-qyrusai-and-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T16:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how QyrusAI and Amazon Bedrock are revolutionizing shift-left testing, enabling teams to deliver better software faster. Amazon Bedrock is a fully managed service that allows businesses to build and scale generative AI applications using foundation models (FMs) from leading AI providers. It enables seamless integration with AWS services, offering customization, security, and scalability without managing infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ameet Deshpande, Vatsal Saglani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate video insights for contextual advertising using Amazon Bedrock Data Automation]]></title>
        <id>2c44c98250b563d96cd62255ed1046fbfb27f28e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/automate-video-insights-for-contextual-advertising-using-amazon-bedrock-data-automation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T16:47:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Data Automation (BDA) is a new managed feature powered by FMs in Amazon Bedrock. BDA extracts structured outputs from unstructured content—including documents, images, video, and audio—while alleviating the need for complex custom workflows. In this post, we demonstrate how BDA automatically extracts rich video insights such as chapter segments and audio segments, detects text in scenes, and classifies Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) taxonomies, and then uses these insights to build a nonlinear ads solution to enhance contextual advertising effectiveness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Burkleaux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Salesforce achieves high-performance model deployment with Amazon SageMaker AI]]></title>
        <id>d3a73cadab6fe23fdc5cece6e7338acaf580d25c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/how-salesforce-achieves-high-performance-model-deployment-with-amazon-sagemaker-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T16:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is a joint collaboration between Salesforce and AWS and is being cross-published on both the Salesforce Engineering Blog and the AWS Machine Learning Blog. The Salesforce AI Model Serving team is working to push the boundaries of natural language processing and AI capabilities for enterprise applications. Their key focus areas include optimizing large […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rielah De Jesus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Amazon EKS troubleshooting using an Amazon Bedrock agentic workflow]]></title>
        <id>7ee99f509b5c4cd129bd088849d2c765155cff78</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/automate-amazon-eks-troubleshooting-using-an-amazon-bedrock-agentic-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T20:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we demonstrate how to orchestrate multiple Amazon Bedrock agents to create a sophisticated Amazon EKS troubleshooting system. By enabling collaboration between specialized agents—deriving insights from K8sGPT and performing actions through the ArgoCD framework—you can build a comprehensive automation that identifies, analyzes, and resolves cluster issues with minimal human intervention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Venkataraman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Host concurrent LLMs with LoRAX]]></title>
        <id>667853f669be33e9aad6de15c701a96537cba1e8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/host-concurrent-llms-with-lorax/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T19:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore how Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA) can be used to address these challenges effectively. Specifically, we discuss using LoRA serving with LoRA eXchange (LoRAX) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) GPU instances, allowing organizations to efficiently manage and serve their growing portfolio of fine-tuned models, optimize costs, and provide seamless performance for their customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kitaoka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a computer vision-based asset inventory application with low or no training]]></title>
        <id>e326ccc136d794a47ea3cca93d24f56235827ad8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-a-computer-vision-based-asset-inventory-application-with-low-or-no-training/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T19:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we present a solution using generative AI and large language models (LLMs) to alleviate the time-consuming and labor-intensive tasks required to build a computer vision application, enabling you to immediately start taking pictures of your asset labels and extract the necessary information to update the inventory using AWS services]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elisabetta Castellano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clario enhances the quality of the clinical trial documentation process with Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>49234d6900b93c10000923535317b636c87d9ace</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/clario-enhances-the-quality-of-the-clinical-trial-documentation-process-with-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T17:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collaboration between Clario and AWS demonstrated the potential of AWS AI and machine learning (AI/ML) services and generative AI models, such as Anthropic’s Claude, to streamline document generation processes in the life sciences industry and, specifically, for complicated clinical trial processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Nguyen, Shyam Banuprakash</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Mixtral 8x7B on Amazon SageMaker with AWS Inferentia2]]></title>
        <id>6cbc32a8b2d4b6fd829c36f935e4e67f4cf60085</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/optimizing-mixtral-8x7b-on-amazon-sagemaker-with-aws-inferentia2/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T17:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how to deploy and serve the Mixtral 8x7B language model on AWS Inferentia2 instances for cost-effective, high-performance inference. We'll walk through model compilation using Hugging Face Optimum Neuron, which provides a set of tools enabling straightforward model loading, training, and inference, and the Text Generation Inference (TGI) Container, which has the toolkit for deploying and serving LLMs with Hugging Face.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lior Sadan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevate business productivity with Amazon Q and Amazon Connect]]></title>
        <id>6ba7698fcbae7600ff9437d516e45a73b8012a62</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/elevate-business-productivity-with-amazon-q-and-amazon-connect/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T17:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we demonstrate how to elevate business productivity by leveraging Amazon Q to provide insights that enable research, data analysis, and report potential fraud cases within Amazon Connect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sujatha Dantuluri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build multi-agent systems with LangGraph and Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>e34b849cc972cfe09bef67955216498f74f95777</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-multi-agent-systems-with-langgraph-and-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T16:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how to integrate open-source multi-agent framework, LangGraph, with Amazon Bedrock. It explains how to use LangGraph and Amazon Bedrock to build powerful, interactive multi-agent applications that use graph-based orchestration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jagdeep Singh Soni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic text-to-SQL for enterprise workloads with Amazon Bedrock Agents]]></title>
        <id>6fb7b0495fdbcebc1c495bd994fbb60b2a4617cd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/dynamic-text-to-sql-for-enterprise-workloads-with-amazon-bedrock-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T16:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how enterprises can implement a scalable agentic text-to-SQL solution using Amazon Bedrock Agents, with advanced error-handling tools and automated schema discovery to enhance database query efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jiwon Yeom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SRE Weekly Issue #472]]></title>
        <id>https://sreweekly.com/?p=1628</id>
        <link href="https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-472/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T01:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: We’ve just raised $62M at incident.io to build AI agents that resolve incidents with you. See how we’re pioneering a new era of incident management. https://go.incident.io/blog/incident.io-raises-62m Scaling Nextdoor’s Datastores: Part 4 In this part of the Scaling Nextdoor’s Datastores blog series, we will see how the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6214</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/04/13/florida-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T08:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can hardly believe it’s been 15y since I did a post on this. I guess our biennial trips through to 2018 were similar enough to not really justify full reports. Though 2014 was quite different as $son0 and I did our PADI Open Water certification, which was a major distraction from the parks. Then […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.thestateofme.com/?p=6214</id>
        <link href="http://blog.thestateofme.com/2025/04/13/florida-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T08:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can hardly believe it’s been 15y since I did a post on this. I guess our biennial trips through to 2018 were similar enough to not really justify full reports. Though 2014 was quite different as $son0 and I did our PADI Open Water certification, which was a major distraction from the parks. Then […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Swan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[冬去春来]]></title>
        <id>https://liuning0820.github.io/2025/04/13/%E5%86%AC%E5%8E%BB%E6%98%A5%E6%9D%A5.html</id>
        <link href="https://liuning0820.github.io/2025/04/13/%E5%86%AC%E5%8E%BB%E6%98%A5%E6%9D%A5.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[树与寒鸦：冬去春来的启示 二月的一个清晨，偶然驻足小区一棵光秃秃的树下，心生感触：这棵树是怎么熬过那严酷的寒冬？ 正思索间，一只寒鸦落在了树枝上，短暂停留。它的出现，让我联想到，是否正是有了寒鸦的片留停留的作伴，才让这棵树在孤独中找到了支撑，从而挺过了寒冬？ 接连数日，我记录下了这棵树的变化，从最初的孤单到逐渐焕发新生，见证了它如何在春光中复苏。 这使我不禁联想到人生亦是如此，寒来暑往，冬去春来，我们每个人都会经历低谷和高峰。在这过程中，找到支撑我们的信念至关重要，无论是家人的鼓励、朋友的支持，还是内心深处那份不灭的希望，都是我们在漫长寒冬中的寒鸦，为我们带来继续前行的力量。 正如那棵树，在最艰难的时刻找到了生存的意义，我们也应在逆境中寻找属于自己的光芒，怀抱希望，坚定地走向未来。这样，无论面对何种困难，我们都能够像这棵树一样，迎来属于自己的春天。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Toby Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an AIOps chatbot with Amazon Q Business custom plugins]]></title>
        <id>893eb38706d37a76b293ad637e9500feca29f0d4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/building-an-aiops-chatbot-with-amazon-q-business-custom-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T17:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we demonstrate how you can use custom plugins for Amazon Q Business to build a chatbot that can interact with multiple APIs using natural language prompts. We showcase how to build an AIOps chatbot that enables users to interact with their AWS infrastructure through natural language queries and commands. The chatbot is capable of handling tasks such as querying the data about Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) ports and Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) buckets access settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Upendra V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TransPerfect Improved Translation Quality and Efficiency Using Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>c68a587504a8f1066bc6492787e67120fd3dd4e6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/how-transperfect-improved-translation-quality-and-efficiency-using-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T17:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post describes how the AWS Customer Channel Technology – Localization Team worked with TransPerfect to integrate Amazon Bedrock into the GlobalLink translation management system, a cloud-based solution designed to help organizations manage their multilingual content and translation workflows. Organizations use TransPerfect’s solution to rapidly create and deploy content at scale in multiple languages using AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Chung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racing beyond DeepRacer: Debut of the AWS LLM League]]></title>
        <id>57251eef5036c4016bbcd24a6292d5c1be91b7b9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/racing-beyond-deepracer-debut-of-the-aws-llm-league/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T17:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS LLM League was designed to lower the barriers to entry in generative AI model customization by providing an experience where participants, regardless of their prior data science experience, could engage in fine-tuning LLMs. Using Amazon SageMaker JumpStart, attendees were guided through the process of customizing LLMs to address real business challenges adaptable to their domain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vincent Oh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>